[
  {
    "question": {
      "questionText": "What country have this flag?",
      "questionUrl": "https://www.worldometers.info/img/flags/is-flag.gif"
    },
    "wrongAnswers": ["Vietnam", "China", "Croatia"],
    "wrightAns": "Israel"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "questionText": "What country have this flag?",
      "questionUrl": "https://www.worldometers.info/img/flags/it-flag.gif"
    },
    "wrongAnswers": ["Mexico", "Hungary", "France"],
    "wrightAns": "Italy"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "questionText": "What country have this flag?",
      "questionUrl": "https://www.worldometers.info/img/flags/ja-flag.gif"
    },
    "wrongAnswers": ["Bangladesh", "India", "Pakistan"],
    "wrightAns": "Japan"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "questionText": "What country have this flag?",
      "questionUrl": "https://www.worldometers.info/img/flags/mx-flag.gif"
    },
    "wrongAnswers": ["Italy", "France", "Netherlands"],
    "wrightAns": "Mexico"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "questionText": "What country have this flag?",
      "questionUrl": "https://www.worldometers.info/img/flags/mg-flag.gif"
    },
    "wrongAnswers": ["China", "Bangladesh", "Aphganistan"],
    "wrightAns": "Mongolia"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "questionText": "What country have this flag?",
      "questionUrl": "https://www.worldometers.info/img/flags/md-flag.gif"
    },
    "wrongAnswers": ["Andora", "Romania", "Columbia"],
    "wrightAns": "Moldova"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "questionText": "What country have this flag?",
      "questionUrl": "https://www.worldometers.info/img/flags/small/tn_ks-flag.gif"
    },
    "wrongAnswers": ["North Korea", "Georgia", "Sweden"],
    "wrightAns": "South Korea"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "questionText": "What country have this flag?",
      "questionUrl": "https://www.worldometers.info/img/flags/sp-flag.gif"
    },
    "wrongAnswers": ["Portugal", "Brazil", "Germany"],
    "wrightAns": "Spain"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "questionText": "What country have this flag?",
      "questionUrl": "https://www.worldometers.info/img/flags/tu-flag.gif"
    },
    "wrongAnswers": ["Egypt", "Syria", "Iran"],
    "wrightAns": "Turkey"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "questionText": "What country have this flag?",
      "questionUrl": "https://www.worldometers.info/img/flags/uk-flag.gif"
    },
    "wrongAnswers": ["Australia", "New Zealand", "Fiji"],
    "wrightAns": "United Kingdom"
  },
  {
    "question": {
      "questionText": "What country have this flag?",
      "questionUrl": "https://www.worldometers.info/img/flags/vm-flag.gif"
    },
    "wrongAnswers": ["China", "Laos", "Thailand"],
    "wrightAns": "Vietnam"
  }
]
